const level15questions = [
          
{
    question: "65 - 57 = ?",
    options: ["8", "87", "6", "18"],
    answer: "18"
},
{
    question: "42 - 39 = ?",
    options: ["58", "61", "93", "3"],
    answer: "3"
},
{
    question: "73 - 40 = ?",
    options: ["56", "33", "63", "67"],
    answer: "33"
},
{
    question: "84 - 65 = ?",
    options: ["12", "4", "19", "5"],
    answer: "19"
},
{
    question: "83 - 69 = ?",
    options: ["53", "47", "11", "14"],
    answer: "14"
},
{
    question: "94 - 54 = ?",
    options: ["91", "97", "40", "64"],
    answer: "40"
},
{
    question: "78 - 31 = ?",
    options: ["35", "79", "47", "92"],
    answer: "47"
},
{
    question: "98 - 41 = ?",
    options: ["57", "96", "23", "79"],
    answer: "57"
},
{
    question: "53 - 38 = ?",
    options: ["8", "24", "15", "95"],
    answer: "15"
},
{
    question: "81 - 70 = ?",
    options: ["11", "51", "48", "68"],
    answer: "11"
},
{
    question: "85 - 41 = ?",
    options: ["35", "36", "44", "61"],
    answer: "44"
},
{
    question: "42 - 33 = ?",
    options: ["43", "54", "9", "36"],
    answer: "9"
},
{
    question: "37 - 37 = ?",
    options: ["1", "97", "96", "0"],
    answer: "0"
},
{
    question: "86 - 17 = ?",
    options: ["19", "93", "69", "77"],
    answer: "69"
},
{
    question: "31 - 13 = ?",
    options: ["18", "13", "85", "72"],
    answer: "18"
},
{
    question: "84 - 25 = ?",
    options: ["41", "59", "6", "94"],
    answer: "59"
},
{
    question: "64 - 23 = ?",
    options: ["18", "41", "60", "9"],
    answer: "41"
},
{
    question: "79 - 76 = ?",
    options: ["70", "41", "3", "72"],
    answer: "3"
},
{
    question: "73 - 59 = ?",
    options: ["50", "14", "76", "47"],
    answer: "14"
},
{
    question: "89 - 18 = ?",
    options: ["92", "71", "70", "6"],
    answer: "71"
},
{
    question: "59 - 40 = ?",
    options: ["19", "95", "26", "30"],
    answer: "19"
},
{
    question: "89 - 66 = ?",
    options: ["26", "23", "56", "18"],
    answer: "23"
},
{
    question: "88 - 84 = ?",
    options: ["35", "4", "7", "21"],
    answer: "4"
},
{
    question: "89 - 39 = ?",
    options: ["81", "60", "50", "26"],
    answer: "50"
},
{
    question: "71 - 59 = ?",
    options: ["8", "11", "82", "12"],
    answer: "12"
},
{
    question: "84 - 16 = ?",
    options: ["4", "36", "68", "74"],
    answer: "68"
},
{
    question: "61 - 53 = ?",
    options: ["29", "46", "8", "6"],
    answer: "8"
},
{
    question: "46 - 15 = ?",
    options: ["80", "54", "31", "94"],
    answer: "31"
},
{
    question: "63 - 58 = ?",
    options: ["5", "10", "91", "44"],
    answer: "5"
},
{
    question: "79 - 38 = ?",
    options: ["88", "41", "18", "67"],
    answer: "41"
},
{
    question: "18 - 17 = ?",
    options: ["1", "38", "41", "24"],
    answer: "1"
},
{
    question: "61 - 61 = ?",
    options: ["17", "89", "6", "0"],
    answer: "0"
},
{
    question: "91 - 21 = ?",
    options: ["54", "70", "46", "15"],
    answer: "70"
},
{
    question: "82 - 57 = ?",
    options: ["8", "25", "46", "15"],
    answer: "25"
},
{
    question: "87 - 58 = ?",
    options: ["97", "50", "52", "29"],
    answer: "29"
},
{
    question: "45 - 12 = ?",
    options: ["33", "12", "8", "4"],
    answer: "33"
},
{
    question: "92 - 35 = ?",
    options: ["34", "75", "57", "3"],
    answer: "57"
},
{
    question: "64 - 18 = ?",
    options: ["77", "46", "36", "89"],
    answer: "46"
},
{
    question: "65 - 25 = ?",
    options: ["21", "9", "40", "61"],
    answer: "40"
},
{
    question: "87 - 18 = ?",
    options: ["66", "8", "69", "46"],
    answer: "69"
},
{
    question: "71 - 17 = ?",
    options: ["48", "41", "13", "54"],
    answer: "54"
},
{
    question: "58 - 33 = ?",
    options: ["25", "46", "20", "1"],
    answer: "25"
},
{
    question: "23 - 17 = ?",
    options: ["99", "10", "79", "6"],
    answer: "6"
},
{
    question: "39 - 36 = ?",
    options: ["64", "39", "92", "3"],
    answer: "3"
},
{
    question: "45 - 19 = ?",
    options: ["19", "59", "26", "48"],
    answer: "26"
},
{
    question: "85 - 43 = ?",
    options: ["17", "12", "76", "42"],
    answer: "42"
},
{
    question: "96 - 40 = ?",
    options: ["13", "51", "56", "39"],
    answer: "56"
},
{
    question: "38 - 17 = ?",
    options: ["76", "80", "21", "6"],
    answer: "21"
},
{
    question: "98 - 48 = ?",
    options: ["50", "18", "66", "25"],
    answer: "50"
},
{
    question: "34 - 32 = ?",
    options: ["3", "2", "98", "22"],
    answer: "2"
},
{
    question: "46 - 19 = ?",
    options: ["90", "1", "15", "27"],
    answer: "27"
},
{
    question: "64 - 43 = ?",
    options: ["47", "9", "21", "42"],
    answer: "21"
},
{
    question: "78 - 41 = ?",
    options: ["27", "54", "37", "29"],
    answer: "37"
},
{
    question: "73 - 17 = ?",
    options: ["56", "64", "1", "45"],
    answer: "56"
},
{
    question: "91 - 41 = ?",
    options: ["53", "55", "50", "87"],
    answer: "50"
},
{
    question: "79 - 50 = ?",
    options: ["23", "33", "87", "29"],
    answer: "29"
},
{
    question: "18 - 12 = ?",
    options: ["82", "52", "6", "79"],
    answer: "6"
},
{
    question: "78 - 50 = ?",
    options: ["6", "28", "49", "24"],
    answer: "28"
},
{
    question: "71 - 64 = ?",
    options: ["7", "4", "69", "58"],
    answer: "7"
},
{
    question: "79 - 43 = ?",
    options: ["1", "36", "75", "83"],
    answer: "36"
},
{
    question: "32 - 11 = ?",
    options: ["75", "76", "77", "21"],
    answer: "21"
},
{
    question: "50 - 27 = ?",
    options: ["23", "80", "78", "55"],
    answer: "23"
},
{
    question: "76 - 22 = ?",
    options: ["60", "21", "54", "5"],
    answer: "54"
},
{
    question: "98 - 72 = ?",
    options: ["26", "97", "19", "2"],
    answer: "26"
},
{
    question: "94 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["76", "84", "70", "46"],
    answer: "84"
},
{
    question: "80 - 20 = ?",
    options: ["60", "88", "84", "52"],
    answer: "60"
},
{
    question: "89 - 62 = ?",
    options: ["27", "83", "5", "35"],
    answer: "27"
},
{
    question: "83 - 20 = ?",
    options: ["70", "84", "14", "63"],
    answer: "63"
},
{
    question: "49 - 42 = ?",
    options: ["93", "3", "95", "7"],
    answer: "7"
},
{
    question: "80 - 50 = ?",
    options: ["30", "75", "18", "82"],
    answer: "30"
},
{
    question: "37 - 26 = ?",
    options: ["11", "95", "12", "82"],
    answer: "11"
},
{
    question: "95 - 62 = ?",
    options: ["64", "88", "97", "33"],
    answer: "33"
},
{
    question: "66 - 65 = ?",
    options: ["28", "40", "61", "1"],
    answer: "1"
},
{
    question: "85 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["65", "25", "19", "75"],
    answer: "75"
},
{
    question: "96 - 11 = ?",
    options: ["11", "98", "47", "85"],
    answer: "85"
},
{
    question: "42 - 35 = ?",
    options: ["7", "39", "93", "95"],
    answer: "7"
},
{
    question: "68 - 34 = ?",
    options: ["15", "8", "70", "34"],
    answer: "34"
},
{
    question: "88 - 33 = ?",
    options: ["55", "93", "31", "33"],
    answer: "55"
},
{
    question: "46 - 33 = ?",
    options: ["13", "29", "39", "30"],
    answer: "13"
},
{
    question: "39 - 10 = ?",
    options: ["18", "53", "29", "71"],
    answer: "29"
},
{
    question: "39 - 19 = ?",
    options: ["67", "20", "52", "87"],
    answer: "20"
},
{
    question: "86 - 78 = ?",
    options: ["71", "64", "8", "97"],
    answer: "8"
},
{
    question: "63 - 14 = ?",
    options: ["7", "49", "6", "87"],
    answer: "49"
},
{
    question: "31 - 15 = ?",
    options: ["64", "85", "16", "68"],
    answer: "16"
},
{
    question: "41 - 41 = ?",
    options: ["57", "56", "0", "36"],
    answer: "0"
},
{
    question: "82 - 23 = ?",
    options: ["36", "59", "57", "28"],
    answer: "59"
},
{
    question: "60 - 58 = ?",
    options: ["95", "82", "85", "2"],
    answer: "2"
},
{
    question: "62 - 29 = ?",
    options: ["52", "0", "79", "33"],
    answer: "33"
},
{
    question: "90 - 50 = ?",
    options: ["91", "38", "32", "40"],
    answer: "40"
},
{
    question: "44 - 19 = ?",
    options: ["90", "25", "96", "12"],
    answer: "25"
},
{
    question: "48 - 28 = ?",
    options: ["20", "33", "34", "66"],
    answer: "20"
},
{
    question: "94 - 18 = ?",
    options: ["16", "42", "76", "36"],
    answer: "76"
},
{
    question: "85 - 13 = ?",
    options: ["16", "10", "89", "72"],
    answer: "72"
},
{
    question: "46 - 27 = ?",
    options: ["77", "19", "23", "38"],
    answer: "19"
},
{
    question: "43 - 26 = ?",
    options: ["12", "27", "17", "74"],
    answer: "17"
},
{
    question: "93 - 88 = ?",
    options: ["56", "74", "5", "9"],
    answer: "5"
},
{
    question: "93 - 33 = ?",
    options: ["29", "12", "60", "82"],
    answer: "60"
},
{
    question: "93 - 83 = ?",
    options: ["10", "46", "84", "93"],
    answer: "10"
},
{
    question: "59 - 22 = ?",
    options: ["61", "5", "47", "37"],
    answer: "37"
},
{
    question: "95 - 79 = ?",
    options: ["28", "16", "72", "78"],
    answer: "16"
},
{
    question: "822 - 399 = ?",
    options: ["918", "698", "423", "208"],
    answer: "423"
},
{
    question: "977 - 397 = ?",
    options: ["901", "580", "83", "607"],
    answer: "580"
},
{
    question: "952 - 171 = ?",
    options: ["589", "549", "781", "5"],
    answer: "781"
},
{
    question: "494 - 181 = ?",
    options: ["313", "305", "760", "386"],
    answer: "313"
},
{
    question: "905 - 310 = ?",
    options: ["716", "475", "849", "595"],
    answer: "595"
},
{
    question: "772 - 163 = ?",
    options: ["609", "203", "919", "811"],
    answer: "609"
},
{
    question: "789 - 377 = ?",
    options: ["817", "412", "237", "245"],
    answer: "412"
},
{
    question: "863 - 305 = ?",
    options: ["558", "987", "277", "911"],
    answer: "558"
},
{
    question: "949 - 710 = ?",
    options: ["284", "595", "916", "239"],
    answer: "239"
},
{
    question: "686 - 533 = ?",
    options: ["153", "711", "298", "683"],
    answer: "153"
},
{
    question: "542 - 352 = ?",
    options: ["729", "528", "274", "190"],
    answer: "190"
},
{
    question: "962 - 136 = ?",
    options: ["354", "465", "972", "826"],
    answer: "826"
},
{
    question: "265 - 143 = ?",
    options: ["35", "790", "122", "173"],
    answer: "122"
},
{
    question: "430 - 408 = ?",
    options: ["152", "668", "22", "464"],
    answer: "22"
},
{
    question: "628 - 283 = ?",
    options: ["776", "345", "249", "438"],
    answer: "345"
},
{
    question: "826 - 729 = ?",
    options: ["589", "524", "870", "97"],
    answer: "97"
},
{
    question: "988 - 587 = ?",
    options: ["512", "49", "401", "377"],
    answer: "401"
},
{
    question: "485 - 331 = ?",
    options: ["677", "154", "809", "608"],
    answer: "154"
},
{
    question: "903 - 857 = ?",
    options: ["380", "46", "101", "406"],
    answer: "46"
},
{
    question: "736 - 726 = ?",
    options: ["585", "146", "10", "671"],
    answer: "10"
},
{
    question: "645 - 503 = ?",
    options: ["67", "323", "768", "142"],
    answer: "142"
},
{
    question: "677 - 186 = ?",
    options: ["510", "992", "902", "491"],
    answer: "491"
},
{
    question: "777 - 404 = ?",
    options: ["873", "888", "373", "503"],
    answer: "373"
},
{
    question: "177 - 147 = ?",
    options: ["434", "30", "630", "904"],
    answer: "30"
},
{
    question: "364 - 125 = ?",
    options: ["239", "206", "408", "386"],
    answer: "239"
},
{
    question: "979 - 881 = ?",
    options: ["441", "345", "98", "374"],
    answer: "98"
},
{
    question: "861 - 291 = ?",
    options: ["200", "70", "128", "570"],
    answer: "570"
},
{
    question: "240 - 215 = ?",
    options: ["492", "379", "389", "25"],
    answer: "25"
},
{
    question: "533 - 119 = ?",
    options: ["638", "630", "527", "414"],
    answer: "414"
},
{
    question: "712 - 588 = ?",
    options: ["866", "321", "124", "901"],
    answer: "124"
},
{
    question: "422 - 308 = ?",
    options: ["114", "69", "905", "358"],
    answer: "114"
},
{
    question: "897 - 236 = ?",
    options: ["728", "661", "751", "663"],
    answer: "661"
},
{
    question: "687 - 482 = ?",
    options: ["23", "397", "205", "863"],
    answer: "205"
},
{
    question: "837 - 637 = ?",
    options: ["36", "37", "426", "200"],
    answer: "200"
},
{
    question: "606 - 387 = ?",
    options: ["841", "350", "391", "219"],
    answer: "219"
},
{
    question: "820 - 225 = ?",
    options: ["635", "595", "215", "673"],
    answer: "595"
},
{
    question: "612 - 465 = ?",
    options: ["222", "147", "227", "279"],
    answer: "147"
},
{
    question: "739 - 548 = ?",
    options: ["76", "191", "845", "256"],
    answer: "191"
},
{
    question: "975 - 235 = ?",
    options: ["740", "851", "925", "26"],
    answer: "740"
},
{
    question: "599 - 262 = ?",
    options: ["996", "337", "314", "295"],
    answer: "337"
},
{
    question: "742 - 539 = ?",
    options: ["203", "112", "982", "764"],
    answer: "203"
},
{
    question: "398 - 382 = ?",
    options: ["947", "451", "171", "16"],
    answer: "16"
},
{
    question: "604 - 320 = ?",
    options: ["437", "25", "284", "707"],
    answer: "284"
},
{
    question: "966 - 501 = ?",
    options: ["410", "998", "465", "631"],
    answer: "465"
},
{
    question: "915 - 421 = ?",
    options: ["101", "494", "817", "844"],
    answer: "494"
},
{
    question: "992 - 907 = ?",
    options: ["85", "514", "763", "800"],
    answer: "85"
},
{
    question: "957 - 434 = ?",
    options: ["523", "705", "873", "275"],
    answer: "523"
},
{
    question: "308 - 189 = ?",
    options: ["119", "722", "830", "464"],
    answer: "119"
},
{
    question: "397 - 281 = ?",
    options: ["419", "351", "116", "449"],
    answer: "116"
},
{
    question: "639 - 122 = ?",
    options: ["514", "310", "517", "60"],
    answer: "517"
},
{
    question: "469 - 310 = ?",
    options: ["209", "462", "733", "159"],
    answer: "159"
},
{
    question: "997 - 593 = ?",
    options: ["54", "61", "987", "404"],
    answer: "404"
},
{
    question: "883 - 215 = ?",
    options: ["396", "668", "26", "863"],
    answer: "668"
},
{
    question: "913 - 770 = ?",
    options: ["838", "781", "143", "359"],
    answer: "143"
},
{
    question: "923 - 579 = ?",
    options: ["456", "17", "344", "443"],
    answer: "344"
},
{
    question: "159 - 141 = ?",
    options: ["18", "230", "102", "986"],
    answer: "18"
},
{
    question: "725 - 489 = ?",
    options: ["165", "236", "833", "537"],
    answer: "236"
},
{
    question: "985 - 318 = ?",
    options: ["682", "667", "298", "269"],
    answer: "667"
},
{
    question: "244 - 242 = ?",
    options: ["837", "878", "97", "2"],
    answer: "2"
},
{
    question: "528 - 337 = ?",
    options: ["134", "100", "191", "367"],
    answer: "191"
},
{
    question: "636 - 555 = ?",
    options: ["675", "826", "81", "814"],
    answer: "81"
},
{
    question: "839 - 182 = ?",
    options: ["848", "657", "210", "494"],
    answer: "657"
},
{
    question: "932 - 687 = ?",
    options: ["925", "86", "245", "960"],
    answer: "245"
},
{
    question: "812 - 371 = ?",
    options: ["441", "681", "975", "383"],
    answer: "441"
},
{
    question: "160 - 145 = ?",
    options: ["225", "741", "15", "587"],
    answer: "15"
},
{
    question: "507 - 155 = ?",
    options: ["614", "733", "701", "352"],
    answer: "352"
},
{
    question: "778 - 756 = ?",
    options: ["608", "127", "409", "22"],
    answer: "22"
},
{
    question: "984 - 742 = ?",
    options: ["933", "239", "260", "242"],
    answer: "242"
},
{
    question: "943 - 225 = ?",
    options: ["5", "926", "718", "77"],
    answer: "718"
},
{
    question: "666 - 568 = ?",
    options: ["838", "475", "98", "390"],
    answer: "98"
},
{
    question: "699 - 307 = ?",
    options: ["649", "392", "287", "445"],
    answer: "392"
},
{
    question: "725 - 583 = ?",
    options: ["372", "142", "165", "773"],
    answer: "142"
},
{
    question: "611 - 389 = ?",
    options: ["200", "593", "222", "989"],
    answer: "222"
},
{
    question: "805 - 367 = ?",
    options: ["438", "136", "206", "188"],
    answer: "438"
},
{
    question: "528 - 343 = ?",
    options: ["185", "250", "657", "76"],
    answer: "185"
},
{
    question: "468 - 418 = ?",
    options: ["50", "461", "155", "467"],
    answer: "50"
},
{
    question: "812 - 483 = ?",
    options: ["329", "988", "107", "964"],
    answer: "329"
},
{
    question: "792 - 140 = ?",
    options: ["731", "750", "652", "306"],
    answer: "652"
},
{
    question: "918 - 401 = ?",
    options: ["673", "796", "517", "379"],
    answer: "517"
},
{
    question: "774 - 241 = ?",
    options: ["247", "795", "533", "18"],
    answer: "533"
},
{
    question: "985 - 228 = ?",
    options: ["835", "686", "757", "814"],
    answer: "757"
},
{
    question: "707 - 325 = ?",
    options: ["235", "382", "750", "551"],
    answer: "382"
},
{
    question: "760 - 278 = ?",
    options: ["849", "222", "482", "250"],
    answer: "482"
},
{
    question: "514 - 356 = ?",
    options: ["431", "589", "955", "158"],
    answer: "158"
},
{
    question: "592 - 519 = ?",
    options: ["165", "73", "736", "791"],
    answer: "73"
},
{
    question: "978 - 813 = ?",
    options: ["885", "48", "165", "854"],
    answer: "165"
},
{
    question: "672 - 218 = ?",
    options: ["281", "454", "437", "71"],
    answer: "454"
},
{
    question: "462 - 269 = ?",
    options: ["84", "86", "193", "252"],
    answer: "193"
},
{
    question: "241 - 157 = ?",
    options: ["84", "102", "948", "952"],
    answer: "84"
},
{
    question: "581 - 245 = ?",
    options: ["336", "527", "621", "785"],
    answer: "336"
},
{
    question: "658 - 559 = ?",
    options: ["732", "102", "99", "789"],
    answer: "99"
},
{
    question: "804 - 461 = ?",
    options: ["592", "156", "343", "264"],
    answer: "343"
},
{
    question: "995 - 774 = ?",
    options: ["908", "555", "221", "734"],
    answer: "221"
},
{
    question: "702 - 402 = ?",
    options: ["535", "300", "446", "869"],
    answer: "300"
},
{
    question: "514 - 407 = ?",
    options: ["824", "171", "718", "107"],
    answer: "107"
},
{
    question: "749 - 492 = ?",
    options: ["290", "98", "321", "257"],
    answer: "257"
},
{
    question: "945 - 257 = ?",
    options: ["133", "805", "165", "688"],
    answer: "688"
},
{
    question: "895 - 197 = ?",
    options: ["909", "456", "698", "535"],
    answer: "698"
},
{
    question: "626 - 519 = ?",
    options: ["107", "786", "485", "39"],
    answer: "107"
},
{
    question: "942 - 642 = ?",
    options: ["300", "594", "647", "301"],
    answer: "300"
},
{
    question: "4186 - 4184 = ?",
    options: ["4833", "2", "126", "1110"],
    answer: "2"
},
{
    question: "4582 - 3776 = ?",
    options: ["806", "6081", "1355", "8027"],
    answer: "806"
},
{
    question: "6355 - 2250 = ?",
    options: ["4105", "7741", "3780", "8328"],
    answer: "4105"
},
{
    question: "3266 - 3232 = ?",
    options: ["1562", "34", "3539", "2202"],
    answer: "34"
},
{
    question: "8315 - 3656 = ?",
    options: ["995", "4659", "2766", "8967"],
    answer: "4659"
},
{
    question: "5953 - 2535 = ?",
    options: ["6235", "3418", "5035", "2144"],
    answer: "3418"
},
{
    question: "9925 - 7594 = ?",
    options: ["2331", "465", "3164", "860"],
    answer: "2331"
},
{
    question: "9691 - 5502 = ?",
    options: ["4998", "8703", "4189", "2070"],
    answer: "4189"
},
{
    question: "3377 - 2469 = ?",
    options: ["5468", "762", "908", "6894"],
    answer: "908"
},
{
    question: "5806 - 2644 = ?",
    options: ["540", "5522", "3162", "1726"],
    answer: "3162"
},
{
    question: "5019 - 2638 = ?",
    options: ["2144", "2381", "9710", "2094"],
    answer: "2381"
},
{
    question: "7684 - 5592 = ?",
    options: ["2092", "4665", "6368", "6499"],
    answer: "2092"
},
{
    question: "9642 - 6697 = ?",
    options: ["6515", "3357", "950", "2945"],
    answer: "2945"
},
{
    question: "9247 - 4694 = ?",
    options: ["9291", "2201", "4297", "4553"],
    answer: "4553"
},
{
    question: "9810 - 4859 = ?",
    options: ["4558", "9722", "8864", "4951"],
    answer: "4951"
},
{
    question: "4890 - 2493 = ?",
    options: ["4159", "7240", "3746", "2397"],
    answer: "2397"
},
{
    question: "7381 - 6779 = ?",
    options: ["1408", "602", "4855", "9496"],
    answer: "602"
},
{
    question: "3020 - 2737 = ?",
    options: ["2450", "283", "8809", "1917"],
    answer: "283"
},
{
    question: "3425 - 1438 = ?",
    options: ["7279", "5266", "7462", "1987"],
    answer: "1987"
},
{
    question: "9877 - 3640 = ?",
    options: ["6237", "8526", "2805", "67"],
    answer: "6237"
},
{
    question: "9545 - 7172 = ?",
    options: ["133", "3190", "253", "2373"],
    answer: "2373"
},
{
    question: "4401 - 3336 = ?",
    options: ["8082", "7275", "4560", "1065"],
    answer: "1065"
},
{
    question: "4034 - 2340 = ?",
    options: ["761", "5284", "3521", "1694"],
    answer: "1694"
},
{
    question: "4183 - 2220 = ?",
    options: ["8438", "1963", "8147", "6336"],
    answer: "1963"
},
{
    question: "5928 - 1662 = ?",
    options: ["8121", "4266", "7360", "8327"],
    answer: "4266"
},
{
    question: "3844 - 2627 = ?",
    options: ["8433", "228", "40", "1217"],
    answer: "1217"
},
{
    question: "8204 - 6610 = ?",
    options: ["4115", "492", "3058", "1594"],
    answer: "1594"
},
{
    question: "7161 - 6112 = ?",
    options: ["4977", "9777", "8378", "1049"],
    answer: "1049"
},
{
    question: "9237 - 6243 = ?",
    options: ["4543", "6461", "2994", "9955"],
    answer: "2994"
},
{
    question: "5150 - 1076 = ?",
    options: ["4074", "4516", "3463", "4868"],
    answer: "4074"
},
{
    question: "5054 - 2694 = ?",
    options: ["8430", "3526", "7199", "2360"],
    answer: "2360"
},
{
    question: "9007 - 8635 = ?",
    options: ["372", "2158", "3484", "5675"],
    answer: "372"
},
{
    question: "4124 - 1103 = ?",
    options: ["4949", "4021", "3021", "5198"],
    answer: "3021"
},
{
    question: "6967 - 2953 = ?",
    options: ["5", "3233", "5572", "4014"],
    answer: "4014"
},
{
    question: "7277 - 3537 = ?",
    options: ["3740", "4091", "3537", "9860"],
    answer: "3740"
},
{
    question: "8086 - 6520 = ?",
    options: ["1566", "3159", "5785", "2327"],
    answer: "1566"
},
{
    question: "8301 - 8170 = ?",
    options: ["4807", "131", "3128", "4786"],
    answer: "131"
},
{
    question: "5651 - 4020 = ?",
    options: ["2977", "1631", "1365", "4447"],
    answer: "1631"
},
{
    question: "3528 - 3296 = ?",
    options: ["4901", "232", "8448", "1354"],
    answer: "232"
},
{
    question: "8289 - 4672 = ?",
    options: ["6001", "3617", "7354", "3503"],
    answer: "3617"
},
{
    question: "9412 - 6222 = ?",
    options: ["3190", "5823", "8780", "9411"],
    answer: "3190"
},
{
    question: "4510 - 3846 = ?",
    options: ["2565", "6510", "4999", "664"],
    answer: "664"
},
{
    question: "2824 - 2055 = ?",
    options: ["769", "6864", "2451", "1298"],
    answer: "769"
},
{
    question: "2434 - 1643 = ?",
    options: ["5640", "2484", "791", "5263"],
    answer: "791"
},
{
    question: "8485 - 3772 = ?",
    options: ["6672", "3888", "4713", "9762"],
    answer: "4713"
},
{
    question: "8811 - 1160 = ?",
    options: ["8575", "3352", "7651", "3965"],
    answer: "7651"
},
{
    question: "9592 - 7368 = ?",
    options: ["8612", "5104", "2224", "5106"],
    answer: "2224"
},
{
    question: "3557 - 3492 = ?",
    options: ["6913", "65", "3167", "1935"],
    answer: "65"
},
{
    question: "4450 - 1737 = ?",
    options: ["2713", "641", "7036", "1694"],
    answer: "2713"
},
{
    question: "9563 - 3279 = ?",
    options: ["9049", "9751", "6284", "4325"],
    answer: "6284"
},
{
question: "After 4060?",
options: ["1396", "8173", "8262", "4382"],
answer: "1396",
},
{
question: "After 8767?",
options: ["947", "8819", "4684", "6599"],
answer: "947",
},
{
question: "After 3862?",
options: ["6315", "452", "8533", "126"],
answer: "452",
},
{
question: "After 1423?",
options: ["1354", "1662", "9474", "959"],
answer: "1662",
},
{
question: "After 2895?",
options: ["9187", "6104", "1205", "28"],
answer: "1205",
},
{
question: "After 4979?",
options: ["8952", "557", "9069", "5049"],
answer: "557",
},
{
question: "After 6229?",
options: ["5143", "7952", "3249", "1540"],
answer: "1540",
},
{
question: "After 1150?",
options: ["618", "950", "5723", "3267"],
answer: "3267",
},
{
question: "After 1961?",
options: ["8548", "945", "6458", "4006"],
answer: "945",
},
{
question: "After 4180?",
options: ["3482", "9570", "5619", "5444"],
answer: "5444",
},
{
question: "After 3845?",
options: ["6306", "9738", "349", "9202"],
answer: "349",
},
{
question: "After 1354?",
options: ["194", "6100", "4814", "6843"],
answer: "194",
},
{
question: "After 2481?",
options: ["8798", "7523", "8021", "4685"],
answer: "4685",
},
{
question: "After 1146?",
options: ["8862", "905", "9736", "1059"],
answer: "1059",
},
{
question: "After 3930?",
options: ["264", "5456", "162", "7597"],
answer: "5456",
},
{
question: "After 1917?",
options: ["1427", "7043", "4701", "2107"],
answer: "7043",
},
{
question: "After 7803?",
options: ["477", "4579", "2911", "1565"],
answer: "1565",
},
{
question: "After 3151?",
options: ["1331", "6154", "3761", "2303"],
answer: "2303",
},
{
question: "After 5278?",
options: ["4273", "613", "5651", "3569"],
answer: "613",
},
{
question: "After 2890?",
options: ["967", "9658", "8878", "5980"],
answer: "967",
},
{
question: "After 2759?",
options: ["9147", "332", "2154", "9567"],
answer: "332",
},
{
question: "After 2602?",
options: ["356", "8047", "3666", "9427"],
answer: "3666",
},
{
question: "After 1748?",
options: ["8568", "6115", "4987", "6102"],
answer: "6102",
},
{
question: "After 2130?",
options: ["3357", "7310", "9190", "5252"],
answer: "5252",
},
{
question: "After 1811?",
options: ["7443", "6334", "3559", "5004"],
answer: "5004",
},
{
question: "After 2512?",
options: ["5523", "5786", "6101", "1358"],
answer: "1358",
},
{
question: "After 2440?",
options: ["5373", "2353", "611", "4203"],
answer: "5373",
},
{
question: "After 2545?",
options: ["1477", "1396", "279", "9168"],
answer: "279",
},
{
question: "After 2439?",
options: ["4746", "6836", "8627", "3258"],
answer: "3258",
},
{
question: "After 3298?",
options: ["4782", "341", "3992", "2411"],
answer: "2411",
},
{
question: "After 6213?",
options: ["8915", "5989", "1558", "552"],
answer: "1558",
},
{
question: "After 3088?",
options: ["1603", "607", "8221", "4919"],
answer: "607",
},
{
question: "After 2715?",
options: ["4203", "9722", "6463", "390"],
answer: "390",
},
{
question: "After 4198?",
options: ["8430", "7323", "6169", "2602"],
answer: "2602",
},
{
question: "After 2421?",
options: ["4404", "6781", "3385", "1961"],
answer: "1961",
},
{
question: "After 3510?",
options: ["3365", "7075", "1917", "3618"],
answer: "3618",
},
{
question: "After 1094?",
options: ["4610", "2873", "9841", "9164"],
answer: "2873",
},
{
question: "After 3254?",
options: ["723", "3404", "7516", "3796"],
answer: "3404",
},
{
question: "After 6283?",
options: ["6600", "6971", "1177", "2794"],
answer: "1177",
},
{
question: "After 8711?",
options: ["7101", "4757", "5169", "752"],
answer: "752",
},
{
question: "After 3195?",
options: ["4950", "7066", "2801", "4268"],
answer: "2801",
},
{
question: "After 2753?",
options: ["197", "4429", "5576", "5795"],
answer: "5576",
},
{
question: "After 1227?",
options: ["9094", "5762", "917", "3944"],
answer: "3944",
},
{
question: "After 2492?",
options: ["1709", "6196", "520", "9378"],
answer: "6196",
},
{
question: "After 4747?",
options: ["6961", "7242", "5631", "4063"],
answer: "4063",
},
{
question: "After 2309?",
options: ["1132", "5284", "8762", "2895"],
answer: "5284",
},
{
question: "After 2368?",
options: ["7494", "7047", "8371", "6738"],
answer: "7047",
},
{
question: "After 2484?",
options: ["2791", "6875", "8282", "8458"],
answer: "2791",
},
{
question: "After 2385?",
options: ["6401", "6915", "9132", "3478"],
answer: "6915",
},
{
question: "After 4589?",
options: ["6714", "1089", "3086", "3878"],
answer: "1089",
},
];

export default level15questions;